universitystudentmovers.org 2016-11-02

# Privacy | University Student Movers

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

On our site we collect the following:

Name  
Email address  
Mailing address  
Phone number

Information is collected from you when you:

Place an order  
Fill out a form

The information collected from you is used in the following ways:

To process transactions

How do we protect visitor information?

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.  
We do not use an SSL certificate  
• We do not need an SSL because:

Do we use ‘cookies’?

We do not use cookies for tracking purposes

Third Party Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer Personally Identifiable Information.

Third party links

We do not include or offer third party products or services on our website.

Google

We have not enable Google Adwords on our site but we may do so on the future.

California Online Privacy Protection Act

According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:  
Users can visit our site anonymously  
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.  
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’, and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:  
• On our Privacy Policy Page  
Users are able to change their personal information:  
• By calling us

How does our site handle do not track signals?  
We honor them and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?  
We do not allow

COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

We do not specifically market to children under 13

Fair Information Practices

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:  
We will notify the users via email  
• Within 1 business day

We agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors
